very good evening friend isme amazing
why bana kasana aam mirror work he should arrive safe
mission possible andaaz the last
question of 10 hole questions camp in the anand saif
virat gather glue of life in the
days when it's really amazing to take off but you everybody and
toubro 10 questions
regarding road safety and be aware and
create awareness unfortunately feed golden
the last question of the amazing sea cream
is on
this video for driving your that nickel
in mountain ka word aa with black is and
no which might result in a ring of fire on hain
yes will still go alone with the help of
china ka vriddhi chai yes no it save to write a
president should not because you for the change
cover right-click no the answer last question
subscribe and love you are also like
subscribe and rich look change no thank you so
much for winters last question you to
you answer  This question is on the question
screen driving mountain whatsapp
and no which might result do you put there
kwid driving na you did that tomorrow
on mountain and take it here and there is snow or you
can call it area here and there where the
chance of typhoon is
very high so you tell us quickly
what will be your answer this question still go
alone with the help of china's bank
charges you will cover your expenses from china and then go
there can always stay at one
or you don't think that the person
driving there is just that so
you will come back or guy status
adventure it is a lot of fun in this
so we will do all this and last not because you
for the change interruption or you will not do it
because you forgot to bring your thing
what will you do at that time tell us quickly
your name answer and I request
you to please
join this campaign with your friends and your benefit so that
last question you have this last  There is a chance to
win a gift and even after this the
questions will be over, it is important to know here
that next time we will bring some more
exciting things with more exciting
gifts for you, answer the time
and the results of this,
our show comes at 10:00 pm, now speaking of plants, its results are
delicate, so you
can check its results and you
can win many exciting prizes and
request that you also request your family members, your
friends, passion
which is in your life, to participate in the middle
and answer us, Anand
Vesting S2 like this give some, we are getting
marriage with, whoever is
suitable for us, they come and talk to you,
team from Ring Ring Road and give all the
questions and related to route safety and that is,
your routes related and also
request that you select whichever answer
because such
situations come with us on daily basis  It is now
related to road safety and we have a
lot of time, what should we do, the thing you are
selecting here and see,
you will do this, in this situation only, I request
you to please follow it in your life also
because you tell everyone
what we should do and what not, in the video, if
we do not follow that thing then it is
important to take these things in your own way,
now they should go to the court so that
our roles can be
decided and there should not be any problem in future, that is, the
death rate should not increase, these should be decreased,
but there are more mid-range
questions available, wrong driving in
mountains, now after this, no which might result in a
good time with the help of the Tiger
Noida region withdrawal notification, so
quickly register yourself and tell me what is
your answer,
I always request you to
follow these road safety measures only
and always take care of even the smallest things, that
means you can always have an
accident, but if
you drive on gas  You will wear it and use safety gear
like seat belt helmet.
Ramesh Yadav said that there is death rate in road accidents,
we can reduce it, you cannot stop it,
anything can happen when you are on the road, you can
apply brakes, anything can happen here
but we can reduce the death rate
if we take precautions, if
you are driving a car, it is
requested that you are sitting in the front or the back, whether you are
driving or not, you should wear a seat belt, it is mandatory for
you to wear a seat
belt, it is for your safety,
if you are riding a bike
properly, whether you are sitting in the front
or the back, whether you are riding a bike or not,
you should wear a helmet because it is
for your safety, now any
helmet creates a covering over
our back, always buy an ISI marked
helmet and always wear it,
do not buy a helmet that is too tight, it should always
fit as per your requirement, it should
not be too tight, if it is loose then it will
fall and it will come out from under
you and if the helmet is too tight
So it will
create discomfort for you somewhere or the other and ultimately it will
increase distraction in driving, so the
responsibility is of both, those who drive ahead and those who are
driving less should also
fulfill their responsibilities and keep yourself and your profits
safe, this is our only request to you
and right now
you also need to be very careful,
you should not cross the road just like that
and always cross the road from such a place where it is
possible for you
that the drivers can see you because the
cars going on the road
come at a very high speed, they do
not seem to react and your mind should always be ready, that is the
lever crossing or the middle of the road, if the
engine does
not become soft while crossing the road like this then it can be a problem for the driver as well,
now always try to cross the road
either from the zebra crossing or
from the foot overbridge or from the underpass,
even if you have to cross from the middle then do it
very carefully and
always cross the road from the visible side where your vision
increases so that the driver can
see you and you can see the drivers, such a place
Always cross the road with a broom
from behind you or in the middle and do
not do it suddenly by shrinking between such abuses which are placed at the speed divider, this
increases the chances of accidents
and while driving, if you are driving a four wheeler, it is
always very important that
your composure is
not to sit with any such person in the front or make a small child sit in the
front which causes more distraction to you
because children
tease you again and again, sometimes they do something like
tuition, avoid it because what happens is that while
driving, it is very important that you should be focused
on the road with
full attention, so you should not do that thing and if
your distraction increases like Babbar,
you should not talk on the phone, while you are driving, you
need more time here, the
screen which is attached on the outer side, do not keep the
phone inside the paper,
thank you, videos or something is going on in it, then
somewhere the chances of your mind getting
disturbed increase and
when you drive, Udayveer shift the phone inside every
day because you can miss anything.
Now you must have seen many times on the rose that it is
written at that place that if your eyes are diverted, an accident may
occur, then you should not do that thing, you have to be
focused and do your right thing
because your one carelessness can take someone else
's life and your own too, that means
anything can happen to you too, so it is
very important that you take proper care of the scheme, you should take care of the safety of yourself as well as your loved ones,
as you know, actually the last date of
birth school quiz, this is pends last
question of this Holi, champion of the day,
you have only 2 hours to
participate in this, please do participate
and be a part of this puja, this is to
make all roads safe for road safety, it is
connected to all of us somewhere or the other and we are
connected because we work in
different ways, whether he is small or big,
everyone uses the road,
whether it is going to the market, going to a special place,
going to school, going to office,
you can use it anyway.  If you use it then it is the
responsibility of all of us that we should together
shave our daily and decrease the cost of daily wear and tear, so
a single person
cannot change that thing, this is the entire
campaign, this is Mask MP
and we want you to
join us in it and contribute in saving your daily wear,
when can you see the
question on my screen is possible that you prefer
driving, that is, nickel in mountain's word of
the black eyes and no which might result in a
ring of fire option, this is on the help channel
Nov 16 2013 subscribe and for this noble
cause of Gautam Buddha, tell me that you will
use it, in this situation you will
go on your own, then tell me quickly what will you do
in such a situation,
literally its two, this is a very white
subject, how many things are there in it,
if we compare it outside and
compare it in our quantity, then the
people here who are related to daily wear do
not take this thing seriously
All such measures etc. are for their own
safety. They are doing this because of the
challan that if there are cameras somewhere, they will
limit their speed or else they will
wear a helmet. Helmets are also such that they are
broken, have tips,
their bells are not in place, they are dancing here and there, that
Ayodhya driving will not be like that.
If a policeman is standing, then you should
not do that. Helmet is very important if you are
doing 24/7, then helmet is very important for
your health, it
protects you from box head injuries and now
because the 12th position has a
lot of contact on the road march, as a result
if anything happens to them, if an
accident happens, their bike gets
hit here, then the chances of them getting injured are
very very high,
so you should not joke with two wheelers,
now subscribe properly, those who are among them should
subscribe because it becomes
very risky and you also know
that everyone is watching you, at home everyone says that
you are careless, you know  It can be taken and
think how much your family members will be sad
if not, then how many people are associated with someone who
press their feet or give
Buddhahood, so many numbers increase
for life time and I have one request,
when it is there then why do you have to bring that situation,
if they have it then
why is there a situation Nath Nani, then you take
care of those things with us, by becoming a
part of this campaign of freedom from disease, this cream and
keep yourself and your fans safe,
so thank you for this is the search of the
question, the second last question of the deity,
human being will be equipped and does
water of things are recited at things
and Albert Einstein tune share the
status say thank you so much less Mintu or else Kasana
and thank you so much oo that
film